Gold, what is such a concept,
you must have understood by now, if you have been following our channel for
some time, then you must have understood
that insurance has an inch and its
importance, like there are two types of
insurance, life insurance and health
insurance, life insurance should be given to the
earning member of the family, it is called life insurance as
an income replacement for the family,
if there is an earning member in Shamli and the family
is dependent on him for
their needs, if he is not there, then the
family should get one inch and impossible
shoulder at that time, so that they can continue their lifestyle,
this is called life insurance online, it is
necessary only for the earning member on
whom one is dependent, the second one is health
insurance, health insurance is also called,
health insurance is necessary for everyone, she
knows why, so we will talk about that, what are the
questions that you
need to ask before taking a health insurance policy,
before starting the video,
I would like to use my app, my
name is Cooling and Chiku, I am the goods
supplier, I will give you all the benefits with the insurance industry,
Arvind Das, stopped and  I
got the installation and like a running video, the video
is divided into 2 parts, one is the
questions that you should ask yourself, I will
talk about such 4 questions that you have to
ask yourself before taking a dense forest
and there are eight questions that you should ask from
insurance companies, insurance advisors,
you are looking at the installation, you
must have that link, so first of all I will talk about the
questions that you have to ask yourself, the first question that comes to mind
whenever you talk about insurance is
how much coverage is there, that is how much coverage will be right
for you, for this there can be two-three parameters,
one is
where do you live, what is your location,
tier-1 and tier-2, if you are living in the tier-2 areas
where medical expenses are there, then
in that case you will
put a little less insurance, if you are living in the tier-3 area, this is what happens with the
insurance, basically it is a
little less in the premium of tier-1 and tier-2
because the logic is that the
treatment cost is there, or the
treatment cost is a little less in tier-2  If
you have Armaan then I can say that if you have Armaan then you should have a little
more entrance gate into it, a
little less will also suffice for you, meaning
yes, if you have to get the green vegetables done a little
later in the exam then you will get this, it will cost
more, if you have to get it done in the tube then it will cost
less, if you don't want to get the figure then here is
that the accused Armaan is in the city, then insurance of 10 to
15 lakhs is considered as fixed deposit and
descent and forms because
if you see that Malviya has already
taken his insurance and there are four members and if till now in a year due to
blood, we have to
go to the hospital for any express and he has to go to the hospital for the
order of fans bracelet, this point, if this hospital
stay is there then how much is the cost, then our average latest is that
if it costs ₹3000, then if there is
someone else who has to stay in the hospital
in 1 year and if the husband also has to stay in the hospital then the cost
of 3 lakhs is fine,
but if there is any critical illness, any
such disease whose cost is very high
like heart failure, transplant, something like this, then
you  It may cost more money
here, you
can consider this volume minimum side by the tension team,
if you want to take it a little
less, 10 way cover
news on amla, one percent of which we will say,
but we can also ask for love, getting treatment
means you can think, definitely you
can think, so you should take it accordingly, if you
want to get courier red chilli in one, then
definitely there is another hand, if your
income level is segment, then term
insurance is open, that is, short term
final income, that is, if it is that much then it will be right
for the front, so here also there is the
first part of Big Boss and you would like to get
treatment in such a place that I cover
all the matches of your one cup, so if you
want to get it done in a good hospital, then it
is
free time of annual income, leave and
insurance, through which, in another way, look at, secondly,
we will talk about those six policies, you should take
individual, this between center means which one is right, I would like to
tell you what is the difference
between individual and meter  It is individual
that if I take insurance alone,
if I am a family of drivers, then
I should take individual life insurance for all
four of us individually,
we should take separate insurance for
different inches of legs and individually,
like
and
subscribe, you can
subscribe to this channel for ₹10
because all those who come on this channel do
not need hospitalization together,
in that case you
can gift a policy, if you have coverage in front of you, then
if you definitely subscribe to Dadasaheb,
Badokhar family floater
is economically important and make a pencil from it to my family
floater plan, this question also comes that
for yourself and your decisions should be simple,
we can ask the entire amount in one policy, do
n't do this Vikas,
when we take your comments from this, in which
your parents, your family are now
in the policy of earning decisions, now the cream will
decide almost as much as you will present in politics,
first you took separate policies for pant pocket withdrawal, if
you take separate policies for your trusts, even
then the cost will be almost the same  If the
host country has 2 - then the constipation will be more than what you get
and the cost is more than what you get. You are reading
because the team has a flavor.
Plus chances
of loading on the policy of Vestige. There are chances of experience
depending on the division. There may be some
pimples and lottery. If the premium increases, then
instead of keeping it completely positive, that candy
crush quality blood donors day Gu's
Polytechnic College Montessori. Now know that
if you are doing business in the parent company
and it is above the limit then you
also get the benefit of subsidy. So you will click on your policy,
click separately for their policy.
Superhit Hussain for his policy
and if he is above his parents then he can take
filmy beat in section 80 of the policy of Rs 5000.
In this,
many things are done near the policy taking center in which there are friends, that is,
devices in the policy. Ablu or
I should get 14520 quarters, this I
go on vacation and I do
not have my own problem and when in XUV I
may need this pitch and this  The ideal option for using this is to take
health insurance. If you've decided to buy health insurance, the sooner you get it, the better.
And this
meeting is so many answers. If you take it early, you have the
first person to call you.
Because your health
condition is most likely better, the land comes.
You have the option to
choose any insurance policy,
any provider, and
use it as per your wish. If you have any lifestyle problem in the coming years, like
hypertension, diabetes, difficulty, or anything like that,
you won't get the same choice.
And now you'll have to take it,
plus the cost. If you're a patient, you'll be early. The
cost is very important.
You don't know
when a medical emergency will come, which one will happen. So, that's what
you're taking this insurance for. There's a lot of
probability involved in determining
when you might need it.  No less medical
emergency did not come massage if you are a student and you
want an insurance policy through date is written in then all year better next
question comes which is universal question whether to
take corporate insurance or your sand loan insurance so make my detailed video on this reason
cotton george x
vs retail inflation for appointment
properties and working for 10 minutes
with your contact there till then insurance is less then death
leaves company or some of their points
may also change internally then join somewhere else there is
no term insurance
mileage you and leaving aside 120 install
ubuntu on startup enter all then even then
you will not have the option of insurance that
Mukesh is the plant above that in the
last step he says right now I will take
individual in pocket collection later I will
take this in the morning call can be up to 100 whether the loop
condition is same or not you will have to take higher
premium package if you do not get polythene then
one of our international center for policy should
run simultaneously extraordinary question 19
point I had highlighted which section is the
benefit of HD  You will get it if you
think that you should take the benefit of life
insurance then one part of it is that you should
ask yourself now we will
take eight such questions which we have to ask the insurance company
or check in inch and galaxy
before talking to them whether it is
available there as per their capacity or not so
first of all we type this on the cream now the
policy is more memberships not all the
best we are capturing the cost so it is
important for us to see what is covered in the policy
so first of all we should be
happy and this company should check
in the policy that why there is no co payment or chatting
means it may be that the
policy is doing a plate exact 0385 for
finance insurance policy is also
checking you how much difference is there then
definitely I will do it in it, it will definitely be there so to know that
difference the first
rule that you will apply is whether there is co payment
or not it may be that in the one which is already
given it is written that there is 22% co payment
means if you will get the ad area then
20,000  If you do it enough then it will be
equal to your post
card effect, this is also typing like
depression is indigo, we will give this much on room rent,
typing by submit means eggs, if there is
no constipation then only skill is there, then it is
important to see that there is cost difference because
if the batter seems like this, it
means what is the thing due to which there is
cosmetic balance, then you will get to know that
before that, first see whether there are co-
payments or other Champions League matches or
not, policy medical, right now it
seems that you are saving but if there is ever a
hospitalization and a bad belt comes, then
this cost may be very high, you may have to
pay from your pocket, so that is room
rent eligibility, that means your
total to information
department of hospitalization also extends, it depends on the
entire room rent because if you are
taking a normal regular single room then the
section will be salaried, if you are going in deluxe then
that decision will be in the year category
where the last 20 years or and if you
go to ginger green chilli room then one  If there will be a
museum then if you see
what is the room rent limit in this,
suppose it is written in your policy that one per cent
of the amount is your IELTS policy then
1% of the amount is always ₹5000, so if the
eligibility is ₹5000 and you want to get an
8000 plus one, you will have to pay only ₹
3000, secondly everything will be done,
your treatment cards, episode
requests, doctor's visit cost
and even dieting are deducted,
now there are a lot of tele expenses,
so Evangelion 20-30 percent extra you have to
put 20% of your profit, if you are
going for a room rent policy and are taking out a
single room then
try to insist on half of it, do not do
any kind of politics on room rent, so
you may get restrictions on the issue,
what happens is that when we are getting hospitalized or are
in an emergency, then there is
no time to think that
something is necessary, like anything.  I am also getting you admitted,
you don't know that if there is Bigg Boss
then it is better but without the recruitment
or eligibility for 21 Pingal private room
and here you don't have to do life lessons
that how much will I have to pay, how much will the insurance
company give, the list is your pimples, its
coverage is starting, so when you take the policy,
before taking the policy, if you have any pre-
existing diseases then it
means first exit, like there is any old
incident hospitalization, here you take a
license medicine shop or any
such medical history, have a certificate
medical history, if you are taking it on regular basis then it takes a
print out,
before taking the policy, firstly these charges are covered, it will
depend on its top set
up, how much is the stuff, it will be taken out,
saffron insurance companies inform, so
if the generation's key setting is this time
very from 12322 couriers, some
polishing, then how important is it for you,
how soon will it cover the kidney, so when you are
taking the policy, for example, I will take it, if
someone has hypertension, blood pressure
and  They want to take a policy, many
policies are available in the market which provide barriers like
your payer, there can be
many things related to hospitalization,
but
whatever is related to it will be covered after a year or
after this year, waiting period is fine, after a year,
so you should see that your lips are important,
rooms related to that generation,
come as soon as possible, friend, when will one side be covered, the main
other option is that you can subscribe to all the
things, so like
it and
definitely subscribe, you
need network, as
you can see that I am late, then
click on the school button in it, you can see the
hospital list on 350 websites on the Ayodhya verdict,
but you
can see the hospital, which hospital is it or
not, it changes from time to time because
all the questions keep coming, there
are many, some computer, there is a
list of 10,000 hospitals, so that thing is
not like that, you will decide in your minute,
if you ever have to go, if you
should go to the chapters, is that comment or
not  If the number of vitals is dirty, there will be
no benefit. In the policy, if the
hospital is seen urgently, half the locality will automatically go right away. There is
no
capsule button and it is also important to see that the
OTP is of the third party administrator. We all
know that this third party
administrator is a bar party or is
it a Muslim regiment. This is
better because the time zone fold video
reduces because if you want, then the
process is that the hospital will approach
third generation vitamins and a company AB
Corp Ltd. If that P and insurance
company is the same, then the land quality is done by their own team, then a
lot of time is
involved and some processes happen.
You do not need to quote at two places. The
next point needs to be seen is some
money balance like seeing the corporate, whether
you have a convert or not in the existing
policy matter. There is patience,
that if you have positive psychology, which is the
health insurance policy of that you
need to be hospitalized for twenty-fourth, then it is
ready clean dare, that there is
no need for country court, there are some such
treatments.  Those who go in the morning and get
charged in the evening and the treatment is done in it, then the
channel subscription is definitely
not applicable and you get clear, then
cover it, which procedures are there
in your policy, that is the real one and a half procedures for
policy but there is an address that
I make all the comments, so you
can check your policy including the rate, it is
important teacher because nowadays there
is seal benefit in the policies, you should check there is
heart benefit in your policy, this means Surya,
now we call your insurance company limited, the
breakfast is over, the tabla is over, in this year
you and the insurance company get angry,
okay, you turn off, if it is over then the
insurance companies will seal the weather
quality, you will get them, they have different
classes, it will ripple, you can
use criminal or you can
use different glasses or you can use once
or you can use unlimited number of science,
then check in the policy
which free fruit benefit is available,
try to take Baahubali policy, the
receiver benefit is in it  In which it has to be thought
that for unrelated treatment, for
example, we have a policy for four of us and I get
hospitalized, the entire 10 locker is used, that was the
problem, okay, and if I
need it again this year, then there is a problem,
so use it, if there is a clause in my policy itself
that I
can only use it for unrelated treatment, then it will not work for me, it is
better that I follow the one in which there is
no cross that I can
only use unrelated treatment, at this point you
can see balance benefits, that is, how much your
insurance plan is focusing on various benefits, so when
every person takes it,
one thing which is already equipped with us is that if you get any
disease, it will
come to your rescue, but today let's see, a
policy is available in England like Miley
Cyrus, so let's focus only on your glasses,
if you lead a healthy lifestyle, it
gives you some award points, which you can
apply, you can
get pizza for free against the payment, when
you are getting treatment and buying medicines
When Bigg Boss gets 101 and
complimentary health checkup, almost every
company gives you. If you take a policy, then they will
see you once a year that you get your full body checkup done
and set a schedule. If you have any action or
depression, then you will take care of yourself and get
treatment for it, you will
not need hospitalization. So
here it is a win-win situation
for the customer. They
can take care of IT appearances. Secondly, it is
also for the insurance company because they will earn claims
if you take care of your health and
if you limit the time, if someone can find out
what is in your polythene, you can
keep this parameter till the best, you can
set it in the insurance policy. The last
point I would like to like is that you
can check today's last one and their
delivery, so there is a difference in
how much settlement happened. If
you use subscribe, then I am
sharing the link of the website, you
can check it. If the settlement ratio in
English is above 50, please
Subscribe
because you
can subscribe, so
you should
subscribe here
because with regard to the upcoming quit recommendations,
which are the top five companies and
taking the rest of the parameters, then video media
house also stay tuned, these are some things
which you should not worry about,
these 12 questions which I have shared with you,
four for you and eight for the insurance company, it is
important to ask them before taking the policy,
understand this long-term commitment, you are
not taking the policy just because you have taken it today,
next reporter will put in the tomato, you will
see in which bank you are
wasting your time, investing your money
because to be a wing of life
insurance policy, you must definitely
subscribe to the association, I want you to
subscribe very quickly, if you have
not done anything to our channel till now, please
subscribe, if you decide to contain tryptophan, that is
my promise, up the phone
jhal